Hi I'm Ann Myrick and today we're going to talk about outfitting your powder room.
This is a small little powder room.
It has a great fun color in it.
Things you want to think about is you want a nice size mirror.
You want bright lights so people can come in and check their makeup.
Sometimes people will put dimmers in it because they like the mood of a darker powder room also so you could have dimmers in your lights.
You want to be sure that it has the things that you need in a powder room.
You want fresh towels, a lot of times if you are having a group those little paper towels are nice because you can use it and some people are funny about using the same towel so you could put some of those little paper hand towels out and then just use it and throw it away.
You want to be sure that you have soap. I would say in here we have just one of these just little plastic bottles but I would say that for your powder room when you have guests you might want to have just a really nice pretty dispenser because we don't have a lot in this powder room and you don't want a whole lot but what you have in here you want it to be special and pretty so for these little utilitarian bottles you might want to get something that is a little bit nicer.
You want to be sure that your powder room is really clean.
You want to clean around your toilet, you want, when people come in, friends, people are going to, this is where your guests are going to go so you want to be sure that your powder room is very clean, toilet is cleaned out.
You want to have extra toilet paper.
We have a basket in here and the basket, I have magazines along with several rolls of toilet paper so if you are having a party and you are in the other room and somebody needs to come in they can find the toilet paper or whatever they need and not have to hunt you down.
Then also fun rug.
This is a great rug that we found.
It has a lot of color and it just adds fun zip.
You want to be sure if you have a rug in your bathroom or wherever you have little throw rugs that they have a rubber gripper on them for the guests or a family member is not going to slide so just go into your powder room and see if there is everything in it that you need to be able to wash your face, wash your hands, go to the bathroom and just have fun decorating your room.
This is Ann Myrick and that is how to outfit your powder room.